{
    "subject": "resource/Oran_Etkin",
    "predicate": "property/birthplace",
    "object": "resource/Israel",
    "human_readable": "Oran Etkin was born in Israel.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8961560130119324,
            "question": "Is Oran Etkin Israeli?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8016192317008972,
            "question": "Where was Oran Etkin born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6452147960662842,
            "question": "Oran Etkin's birth country is...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6413824558258057,
            "question": "Oran Etkin's birth country is known for...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6052769422531128,
            "question": "What nationality is Oran Etkin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5660238862037659,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Oran Etkin based on his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4967287480831146,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Oran Etkin's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49417436122894287,
            "question": "In which country did Oran Etkin come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46703511476516724,
            "question": "What is Oran Etkin's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4044688642024994,
            "question": "Where did Oran Etkin begin his life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Oran Etkin was born in Israel.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8716_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Oran Etkin's place of origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8716_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country did Oran Etkin come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8716_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Oran Etkin's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8716_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8716_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide strong evidence to support this statement, with multiple mentions of Oran Etkin's birthplace being Israel."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Oran Etkin was born in Israel and later raised in the U.S., supporting this triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}